

#### **PROFILE**

I have a results-focused attitude to creating SPA, using React(JS/TS), Redux.

I have a sufficient experience in React development from small pet projects to large architectural and testable web applications.

My most important skills are problem solving, proactivity and total

Ready to consider project work and fulltime employment.

#### CONTACTS



abzal008suan@gmail.com



+7 952 460 9665



#### **SKILLS**

- REACT / REDUX (toolkit) / MIDDLEWARE
- JAVASCRIPT / TYPESCRIPT
- AXIOS / RESTAPI
- NODE.JS / EXPRESS / MONGODB
- MATERIAL-UI/ANT-DESIGN
- HTML5 / CSS3 / SASS / EMOTION JS
- UNIT TESTS / STORYBOOK
- GIT/GITLAB
- English Upper-Intermediate in progress

### FRONT-END DEVELOPER

# **Abzal Suan**











#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### TravelAsk Mobile App | 2021 Sept - present

- Using React-Native for mobile development
- Class components, SCSS, AXIOS requests
- · Engaged in refactoring, bug fixing.

#### Sberclass outsource team | 2021 July - 2021 Sept

- Creating interactive lessons using React, Hooks, emotionJS
- Engaged in refactoring, bug fixing.
- Reusable components development
- StoryBook components

#### Freelance | 2021 March - 2021 July

- React development using redux, react-redux, react-routerdom, redux middleware
- Work with and migrating to Hooks, TypeScript
- Engaged in refactoring, bug fixing.
- Reusable components development
- Unit Testing and StoryBook components

#### Insen group(beauty and wellness) | Senior manufacturing master | 2020 Apr - 2021 Feb

- Management of the manufacturing area.
- Increasing the efficiency of the team
- Product and service quality monitoring

#### DanceFile | Photographer | 2017 Oct - 2020 Feb

- Shooting and filming in various conditions
- Equipment service
- Processing, design, printing of images

#### **EDUCATION**

#### 2021 March

IT-INCUBATOR

#### 2017 - 2021

Moscow Polytechnic University Electrical engineering (EXTRAMURAL)

#### 2014 - 2017

Almaty College of Transport and Technology Auto electrician



#### обо мне

Я Front-end разработчик, который ориентирован на результат при создании SPA с использованием React (JS/TS), Redux.

У меня достаточный опыт в React проектов, до больших архитектурных и тестируемых web-приложении.

Мои самые главные навыки это умение решать проблемы, проактивность и полный вклад.

Готов рассмотреть предложения о

#### КОНТАКТЫ



abzal008suan@gmail.com



+7 952 460 9665



Москва, Россия

#### НАВЫКИ

- REACT / REDUX (toolkit) / MIDDI FWARE
- JAVASCRIPT/TYPESCRIPT
- AXIOS / RESTAPI
- NODE.JS/EXPRESS/MONGODB
- MATERIAL-UI / ANT-DESIGN
- HTML5/CSS3/SASS/EMOTION JS
- UNIT TESTS / STORYBOOK
- GIT/GITLAB
- progress

## Абзал Суан











#### ОПЫТ РАБОТЫ

#### TravelAsk мобильное приложение | Сентябрь 2021 — по настоящее время

- React-Native для мобильной разработки
- Class компоненты, SCSS для стилей, AXIOS запросы
- разработка reusable компонентов
- был вовлечен в refactoring и bug fixing

#### Сберкласс outsource | Июль 2021 — Сентябрь 2021

- разработка интерактивных приложении с использованием React, Hookc, emotionJS
- разработка reusable компонентов
- написание модульных StoryBook документации
- был вовлечен в refactoring и bug fixing

#### Фриланс I Март 2021 — Июль 2021

- разработка React приложении с использованием redux, react-redux, react-router-dom, redux middleware
- разработка reusable компонентов
- переход и работа с TypeScript и Hooks
- написание модульных тестов и StoryBook документации
- был вовлечен в refactoring и bug fixing

#### Инсен групп | Старший мастер | Апр 2020 — фев 2021

- повышение эффективности команды
- мониторинг качества продукта и обслуживания

## DanceFile | Фотограф/оператор| Окт 2017 — фев 2020

- непосредственный процесс съёмки
- осуществление съемок в различных условиях
- подбор необходимой фототехники и атрибутики

#### **ОБРАЗОВАНИЕ**

#### Март 2021

IT-INCUBATOR

Front-end разработчик (React/Redux/TypeScript)

#### 2017 - 2021

Московский политехнический университет электроэнергетика и электротехника (заочно)

#### 2014 - 2017

АКПТиТ

Автоэлектрик

